313
1 2|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|1 2|0|0|0|0|1 0|1 0|1 0|1 0|1 0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|1 2|0|0|1 2|0|0|1 2|0|0|1 2|0|0|1 2|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|1 2|1 2|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0|0
763
Random number|Generates a random integer.|Font Size|Changes the font size.|Accuracy of operations|Represents accuracy of operations. The larger it is, the more accurate the calculations are, and therefore slow.|Accuracy of numbers|Represents the display accuracy of the numbers.|Number of digits|Represents the number of digits of the random number to be generated.|Number Boundary|Represents one or the other of the two bounds of the digits constituting the random number generated.|Number Boundary|Represents one or the other of the two bounds of the digits constituting the random number generated.|Add|Add a data item to the list. Click to add a number in the text window.|Delete|Delete a data item from the list. Click to delete a number in the text window.